Guide to the Brooklyn Historical Society institutional records ARC.288
Brooklyn Historical Society
Brooklyn Historical Society institutional records
1862-2020
Brooklyn Historical Society
ARC.288
450 Linear Feet in 740 boxes, 4 flat file drawers, and several loose oversize folders.
The records of the Brooklyn Historical Society, founded in 1863 as the Long Island Historical Society. The Society closed in 2020 when it was merged with Brooklyn Public Library to become the Center for Brooklyn History.
Conditions Governing Access
The majority of this collection is open to researchers without restriction. Access restrictions are noted at the series or box level.
Materials in the following series are restricted for 20 years from the date of creation:
Series 2: Board and Committee records
Sub-series 10.1: Grants and Gifts: Government
Sub-series 10.2: Grants and Gifts: Foundations and Non-Profits
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The bulk of these records were collected by the institution as part of its recordkeeping. Materials from external sources are noted as such where possible.
Existence and Location of Copies
Portions of Series 17: Audiovisual materials have been digitized. Consult CBH staff for more information.
Arrangement
The collection is organized in the following series:
Series 1: Administrative files
Series 2: Board and Committee records
Series 3: Executive Director files
Series 4: President files
Series 5: Building records
Series 6: Scrapbooks
Series 7: Curatorial Affairs and Collections
Series 8: Exhibitions and Special Projects
Series 9: Oral History
Series 10: Development
Series 11: Education
Series 12: Programs and External Affairs
Series 13: Marketing and Communications
Series 14: Visitor Services and Retail
Series 15: Publications
Series 16: Financial records
Series 17: Audiovisual materials
Historical note
Founded in 1863, the Long Island Historical Society (LIHS)'s mission was to collect and preserve the "history of the United States, the State of New York, and, more particularly, of the counties, cities, towns, and villages of Long Island." Over time, the institutional mission and collection policy narrowed to focus on Brooklyn history, and in 1985 LIHS changed its name to Brooklyn Historical Society (BHS). With these changes came an emphasis on showcasing Brooklyn's diversity, specifically through community-centered exhibitions and educational programming. In 2020, BHS merged with the Brooklyn Collection at the Brooklyn Public Library to form the Center for Brooklyn History.
Sources:
The Long Island Historical Society Quarterly, vol. 1, no. 1, Jan. 1939, p. 27.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
If digital surrogates exist, they should be used in place of the originals whenever possible.
Related Materials
Library and collections:
-Edna Huntington papers and photographs (ARC.044)
-Edna Huntington photograph collection (V1974.016)
-Emma Toedteberg collection (ARC.079)
-Emma Toedteberg bookplate collection (2012.004)
-Henry Reed Stiles papers (ARC.218)
-Chandos Fulton notes on the history of Brooklyn newspapers (1973.223)
-John D. Morrell photographs (ARC.005)
Presidents:
-Brevoort family papers (1977.285)
-Edgerton G. North papers (1977.323)
Building:
-128 Pierrepont Street building architectural drawings (ARC.302)
Women's Committee:
-Maud E. Dillard papers (ARC.133) (unprocessed)
Exhibitions, Special Projects, and Oral Histories:
-AIDS/Brooklyn Exhibition collection (1993.001)
-Brooklyn photograph and illustration collection (ARC.202) - photos of AIDS/Brooklyn Opening
-The Battle of Long Island: A Bird's Eye View exhibition maps and drawings (ARC.301)
-Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation oral histories (2008.030)
-Borough Hall: Mirror of Change exhibit photograph collection (V1982.003)
-Brooklyn Heights Synagogue oral histories (2011.005)
-Brooklyn Neighborhoods and How They Grew exhibit photograph collection (V1974.034)
-Crossing Borders, Bridging Generations oral history collection (2011.019)
-Crown Heights History Project collection (1994.006)
-Dutch Homesteads exhibit photograph collection (V1974.035)
-Elias Lewis, Jr. letters (2013.002)
-Ford family papers and Long Island Historical Society exhibition records (1978.162)
-Henry R. Stiles collection of Brooklyn Historical Society institutional memory oral histories (2015.030)
-Hispanic Communities Documentation Project records and oral histories (ARC.032)
-In Transit exhibit photograph collection (V1974.033)
-Long Island Historical Society photographs (V1974.031)
-Muslims in Brooklyn oral histories (2018.006)
-New Neighbors: Sunset Park's Chinese Community oral histories (1994.007)
-Prospect Park exhibit photography collection (V1974.036)
-Puerto Rican Oral History Project records (1976.001)
-Voices of Brooklyn oral histories (2008.031)
-West Indian Carnival Documentation Project records (2010.019)
Lectures:
-G. Naphegyi lecture transcription (1977.663)
-John F. Aiken lecture transcriptions (1977.660)
-John Hooper lecture transcription (1977.662)
-Oliver Starr St. John lecture notes on the Battle of Long Island (1973.286)
-William Everett lecture transcription (1977.661)
Membership:
-Cyrus Pyle membership receipts (1977.369)
Other related collections:
-Daniel M.C. Hopping collection of Long Island Historical Society photographs and slides (V1988.052)
-Long Island Historical Society photographs (V1974.031)
-Brooklyn photograph and illustration collection (ARC.202)
-Committee on Brooklyn History records (1977.256)
-Brooklyn Historical Society institutional artifacts (consult CBH staff)
Scope and Contents
The Brooklyn Historical Society Institutional records chronicle the topics, events, and departmental activities that are part of the Society's 157-year history. Materials in this collection provide information regarding the landmark building, exhibits, special projects, the library and archives, public programming, education, the Board of Directors, and much more. In addition to documenting how BHS operated, this collection shows how the Society's mission and policies changed over time, as well as the institution's impact on Brooklyn's history and people.
- Series 1: Administrative records, 1863-2020; 3.34 Linear Feet in 4 document boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and one flat file folder.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged into five sub-series:
  Sub-series 1.1: Annual reports, 1894-2000
  Sub-series 1.2: Constitution and by-laws, 1863-1985
  Sub-series 1.3: Deeds, mortgages, and leases, 1866-1936
  Sub-series 1.4: Staff management, 1976-2020
  Sub-series 1.5: Strategic planning, 1984-2019
  Scope and Contents
  Series 1: Administrative, 1863-2020, includes materials related to top-level management of the Society. These materials include annual reports to members and New York State; by-laws and amendments to by-laws; deeds, mortgages, and leases related to 128 Pierrepont Street; files related to union organizing in the 1970s and 1980s; files related to the 1985 name change from LIHS to BHS; and strategic planning proposals.
  Related Materials
  Related materials can be found throughout the other series in this collection, namely:
  Series 2: Board and committee records
  Series 3: Executive Director files
  Series 4: President files
  Series 5: Building records
  Series 10: Development
  Series 16: Financial records
  - Sub-series 1.1: Annual reports and related documents, 1894-2000; 1894-1966
    This sub-series is arranged chronologically.
    Sub-series 1.1: Annual Reports includes annual reports of the Long Island Historical Society submitted to New York State and sent to members from 1894 to 1958. There are no annual reports from the years 1870-1874 and most of the years post-1966. Annual reports post-1966 can be found in Series 2: Board and Committee records.
    This sub-series also includes examples of annual reports and annual appeals from 1997 to 2000 from other New York City- and Brooklyn-based institutions, such as the Brooklyn Museum.
    - Annual reports, 1864-1999
      - 1864-1865 (Box 553, Folder 3-6)
      - 1866-1868 (Box 552, Folder 1-5)
      - 1869-1882 (Box 554, Folder 1-7)
      - 1883-1885, 1894-1895, 1897-1898 (Box 555, Folder 1-3, 5-6)
      - 1899-1900 (Box 508, Folder 3-4)
      - 1902-1903 (Box 555, Folder 7, Box 556, Folder 1-3)
      - 1903-1910 (Box 508, Folder 5-11)
      - 1910 (Box 556, Folder 4)
      - 1911-1913 (Box 508, Folder 12-14)
      - 1914-1929 (Box 508, Folder 15-30)
      - 1930-1950 (Box 556, Folder 5)
      - "Statutory Reports", 1951-1958 (Box 508, Folder 31)
      - 1956-1966 (Box 556, Folder 6)
      - 1968, 1977, 1987 (Box 557, Folder 1-3)
      - Annual Reports to State, 1894-1937 (Box 508, Folder 1)
      - Annual Report samples, 1997-1999 (Box 557, Folder 4 - 6, Box 508, Folder 32)
    - List of Members of the Long Island Historical Society, circa 1863 (Box 553, Folder 2)
    - List of Members and By-laws of the Long Island Historical Society, 1875 (Box 553, Folder 7)
    - List of Members of the Long Island Historical Society with a Sketch of the Institution, 1876 (Box 553, Folder 8)
    - Proceedings of the Long Island Historical Society in Memory of James Carson Brevoort, Urania Battell Humphrey, John Greenwood, and Alfred Smith Barnes, 1888 (Box 555, Folder 4)
    - [Report of Directors to Members], 1898 (Box 508, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence regarding annual reports, 1905 (Box 553, Folder 9)
    - Brooklyn-based annual appeal samples, 1999-2000 (Box 508, Folder 33-35)
  - Sub-series 1.2: Constitution and by-laws, 1863-1985
    Sub-series 1.2: Constitution and by-laws includes 1863 certificates of incorporation of the Long Island Historical Society and by-laws and amendments to by-laws through the 1980s.
    Further files about amendments to by-laws can be found in Series 2: Board and Committee records.
    - [The By-laws and Certificate of Incorporation of the Long Island Historical Society], 1863 (Box 508, Folder 36)
    - [Copy of the Long Island Historical Society certificate of incorporation], circa 1863 (Box 510, Folder 1)
    - By-laws and membership lists, 1891 (Box 509, Folder 37)
    - By-laws (corrected copy), circa 1895 (Box 557, Folder 7)
    - By-laws, 1900 (Box 509, Folder 38)
    - Extracts from laws (1865-1897?) re: LIHS, circa 1900 (Box 510, Folder 2)
    - Amended Articles of Association and By-laws, 1903 (Box 557, Folder 8)
    - Certificate of incorporation, Articles of association, By-laws, 1939 (Box 557, Folder 9)
    - LIHS By-laws as amended to 1957, 1956-1957 (Box 509, Folder 39)
    - LIHS By-laws as amended to 1967 (Box 509, Folder 40)
    - By-laws, 1984-1985 (Box 509, Folder 41)
  - Sub-series 1.3: Deeds, mortgages, and leases, 1866-1936
    Sub-series 1.3: Deeds, mortgages, and leases includes deeds, mortgages, and leases related to the 128 Pierrepont Street building. The leases are rental agreements between the Long Island Historical Society and various companies for using space on the ground floor.
    Related materials are in Series 5: Building records.
    - Abstract of title of premises corner of Pierrepont and ClintonStreet [and deeds], 1866-1867 (Box 513, Folder 1)
    - Bonds and mortgage to the Misses Thurston, 1866-1878 (Box 513, Folder 2)
    - Mortgages to Mutual Life Insurance Company and Misses Thurston, relates to 128-132 Pierrepont St., 1873 (Box 513, Folder 3)
    - Mortgage papers re: 543 Bergen Street, 1905-1936 (Box 510, Folder 3)
    - Mortgage papers re: 543 Bergen Street, 1905-1936 (Box 510, Folder 4)
    - [Home Insurance Company of New York lease], 1926 (Box 510, Folder 5)
    - [Fidelity-Phenix Fire Insurance Company of New York lease and first floor plan], 1926 (Folder Flat File 11)
    - [Other mortgages], 1930-1933 (Box 510, Folder 6)
    - [Home Insurance Company lease], 1931 (Box 510, Folder 7)
    - [Crum and Forster lease], 1932 (Box 510, Folder 8)
    - [Joseph Gibbs mortgage, 50 Bremen Street], 1934 (Box 510, Folder 9)
    - [Home Insurance Company lease], 1936 (Box 510, Folder 10)
  - Sub-series 1.4: Staff management, 1976-2020
    Sub-series 1.4: Staff management includes files regarding union organizing at the Long Island Historical Society and Brooklyn Historical Society, staff lists, senior meetings, holiday schedules, the Jim Laughlin Executive Director search, and employees from the New York City Department for the Aging.
    Further materials regarding staff management at the Long Island Historical Society and Brooklyn Historical Society can be found in Series 3: Executive Director files and Series 4: President files.
    - [Labor law pamphlets], circa 1976 (Box 510, Folder 11)
    - [District 65 union information], 1976 (Box 510, Folder 12)
    - [District 65 union informational pamphlets], 1976 (Box 510, Folder 13)
    - Union material, 1976 (Box 510, Folder 14)
    - District 65 union material, 1976 (Box 510, Folder 15)
    - Contract: District 65, 1976 (Box 510, Folder 16)
    - [LIHS strike], 1976-1977 (Box 510, Folder 17)
    - [District 65 union cards], 1984 (Box 510, Folder 18)
    - [Union contract], 1985 (Box 510, Folder 19)
    - Union, 1977-1992 (Box 510, Folder 20-21)
    - Staff - BHS, 1986-1993 (Box 509, Folder 6)
    - [Computerized accounting update memo], 1987 (Box 509, Folder 7)
    - Dept. for the Aging, 1986-1995 (Box 511, Folder 1-2)
    - Staff meeting notes, 1995-1996 (Box 511, Folder 3)
    - Jim Laughlin, Executive Director search, 1998-1999 (Box 509, Folder 8)
    - [Holiday schedules], 2005-2006 (Box 509, Folder 9)
    - Senior staff meetings, 2018-2020 (Box 511, Folder 4)
  - Sub-series 1.5: Strategic planning, 1984-2019
    Sub-series 1.5: Strategic planning includes proposals, memos, and correspondence related to organizational and change management processes. Most of the materials relates to the name change process and feedback in the mid-1980s when the Long Island Historical Society changed its name to Brooklyn Historical Society and strategic planning proposals from 2007 to 2019.
    Further files related to strategic planning and fundraising can be found in Series 10: Development.
    - LIHS name change complaints, 1984 (Box 511, Folder 5)
    - Long Island Historical Society name change controversy, 1984 (Box 511, Folder 6)
    - Name change - LIHS Brooklyn Historical Society, 1984-1985 (Box 511, Folder 7)
    - Name change, 1985 (Box 511, Folder 8)
    - Change of name - Restrictions - Laughlin, 1985 (Box 511, Folder 9)
    - [Friends of LIHS, name change], 1985 (Box 511, Folder 10)
    - Certificate of Incorporation [Restatement documents], 1985
    - [Fundraising feasibility study and strategic plan], 1997 (Box 509, Folder 10)
    - 5-year plan, 2007-2008 (Box 509, Folder 11)
    - Strategic planning, 2007-2010 (Box 509, Folder 12-14)
    - Strategic plan 2011 (process), 2009-2011 (Box 512, Folder 11)
    - Strategic planning, 2015, 2019 (Box 512, Folder 12-13)
- Series 2: Board and Committee records, 1863 - 2020
  Conditions Governing Access
  Materials in this series are restricted for 20 years from the date of creation.
  Series 2: Board and Committee records, 1863 - 2020, is arranged into six sub-series:
  Sub-series 2.1: Board of Trustees, Board of Directors, Executive Committee, and Annual Meeting materials, 1863 - 2020
  Sub-series 2.2: Carol Clark Board and Executive Committee files, 1995-2000
  Sub-series 2.3: Jessie Kelly Board and Executive Committee files, 1998 - 2005
  Sub-series 2.4: James Laughlin Building Committee files, 1997 - 2002
  Sub-series 2.5: Board of Trustees biographical files, 1866 - 2018
  Sub-series 2.6: The Women's Committee of the Long Island Historical Society, 1959-1978
  Series 2: Board and Committee records, 1863 - 2020, includes agendas, minutes, meeting preparation packets, memos, and correspondence related to the Board of Trustees, Board of Directors, Executive Committee, and Annual Meetings of the Long Island Historical Society and Brooklyn Historical Society. Materials related to special committees and trustee biographical files are also included.
  - Sub-series 2.1: Board of Trustees, Board of Directors, Executive Committee, and Annual Meeting materials, 1863 - 2020
    Sub-series 2.1: Board of Trustees, Board of Directors, Executive Committee, and Annual Meeting materials, 1863 - 2020, includes agendas, minutes, and memos related to the Long Island Historical Society and Brooklyn Historical Society's Board of Trustees, Board of Directors, Executive Committee, Annual Meeting, and special committees.
    - Board of Directors [minutes], 1863-1881 (Box 547)
    - Directors' minutes, 1863-1903 (Box 550)
    - Minutes of the Executive Committee, 1863-1913 (Box 551)
    - [Finance Committee appropriations request], 1863 (Box 546, Folder 21)
    - [Committee on the Natural History of Long Island], circa 1863 (Box 521, Folder 22)
    - [Board of Directors Natural History Department resolutions], circa 1863 (Box 521, Folder 23)
    - ["History and its Sources," an address read before the Long Island Historical Society at the Annual Meeting, by James Carson Brevoort], 1868 (Box 521, Folder 25)
    - [Report of the Executive Committee], 1869 (Box 521, Folder 26)
    - [Report of the Committee on the Claim of the Brooklyn Trust Company], 1874 (Box 521, Folder 27)
    - Mr. Tayler's report, not presented [Executive Committee], 1874 (Box 521, Folder 28)
    - Report to Executive Committee by Joshua M. Van Lott on resolutions of March 1880 (Box 521, Folder 29)
    - [Executive Committee report], 1880 (Box 521, Folder 30)
    - [Executive Committee, Hamilton Literary Association room request], 1880 (Box 521, Folder 31)
    - [Building Committee, reply to the Mercantile Library Association], circa 1880 (Box 521, Folder 32)
    - [Board of Directors, Reverend Doctor A. P. Putnam], circa 1880 (Box 521, Folder 33)
    - [Board of Directors, Librarian's report], circa 1881 (Box 521, Folder 34)
    - [Circular pamphlet proposal], circa 1881 (Box 521, Folder 35)
    - [Notice of new janitor], circa 1881 (Box 521, Folder 36)
    - [Board of Directors, Hugh Allen death], 1881 (Box 521, Folder 37)
    - [Directors Meeting minutes], 1881 (Box 521, Folder 38)
    - [Treasurer's Report to the Executive Team], 1882 (Box 521, Folder 39)
    - [Directors Meeting, Henry Cruse Murphy death], 1882 (Box 521, Folder 40)
    - Librarian's Report to Board of Directors, 1882 (Box 521, Folder 41)
    - [Resolutions regarding the death of Theodore Dwight], 1883 (Box 521, Folder 42)
    - [Executive Committee, Report to Directors], 1886 (Box 521, Folder 43)
    - [Directors Meeting, Storrs portrait gift acknowledgement], 1887 (Box 521, Folder 44)
    - [Board of Directors, Henry E. Pierrepont death], 1888 (Box 521, Folder 45)
    - [Committee on the Publication of the Washington Letters], 1890 (Box 546, Folder 22)
    - [Committee on Directors' quorum report], 1899 (Box 546, Folder 23)
    - Board meetings [minutes], 1904-1947 (Box 548)
    - [Executive Committee meeting minutes], 1913-1946 (Box 549)
    - Board of Directors - correspondence, 1936 October - 1940 April (Box 521, Folder 46)
    - [Resolutions on the death of Reverend Richard S. Storrs], 1900 (Box 522, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors - correspondence, 1940 May - 1946 April (Box 522, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors - correspondence, 1947 January - 1951 February (Box 522, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors - correspondence, 1951 May - 1953 November (Box 522, Folder 4)
    - Addresses at LIHS Annual Meetings, 1947-1948 (Box 522, Folder 5)
    - Councilors, 1942-1952 (Box 522, Folder 6)
    - Councilors, 1947-1952 (Box 522, Folder 7)
    - Minutes of the LIHS: Executive Committee Meetings, Annual Meetings, Director's Meetings, 1947-1957 (Box 514, Folder 1 - 3)
    - [Annual Meeting invitation cards], 1953-1959 (Box 514, Folder 4)
    - Councilors, 1953-1960 (Box 514, Folder 5)
    - Minutes of the LIHS: Executive Committee Meetings, Annual Meetings, Director's Meetings, 1957-1960 (Box 514, Folder 6 - 8)
    - Special Projects Committee, 1957-1960 (Box 514, Folder 9)
    - Special Projects Committee, 1957-1964 (Box 515, Folder 1)
    - Letters received by Mr. Kuhnast Corresponding Secretary, 1957-1963 (Box 519, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors [correspondence], 1958-1960 (Box 515, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of the LIHS: Executive Committee Meetings, Annual Meetings, Director's Meetings, 1960-1963 (Box 515, Folder 3)
    - [Board of Trustees materials], 1962-1967 (Box 519, Folder 2-3)
    - Minutes of the Long Island Historical Society, 1963-1965 (Box 511, Folder 11-31)
    - Minutes of the Long Island Historical Society, 1966 (Box 511, Folder 32, Box 521, Folder 1-4)
    - Minutes of the Long Island Historical Society, 1967-1970 (Box 521, Folder 5-21)
    - [100th Annual Meeting invitation], circa 1963 (Box 515, Folder 4)
    - Dinner James A. Kelly, 1965-1966 (Box 522, Folder 8)
    - [Annual Meeting materials], 1966-1967 (Box 515, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meetings of Long Island Historical Society invitation cards, 1967 (Box 515, Folder 6)
    - [Report from the Executive Director], 1969 (Box 515, Folder 7)
    - Nominating Committee [Councilors], 1969 (Box 522, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meetings of Long Island Historical Society invitation cards, 1970-1972 (Box 515, Folder 8)
    - [Nominating Committee], 1971 (Box 515, Folder 9)
    - [Executive Committee resolution], 1972 (Box 515, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 515, Folder 11-12)
    - Dickson, Carroll, Director, Board, 1973 (Box 515, Folder 13)
    - Dennon, Lester E., Director, Board, 1973 (Box 515, Folder 14)
    - Gold, Michael, Director, Board, 1973 (Box 515, Folder 15)
    - Annual Meetings of Long Island Historical Society invitation cards, 1973-1976 (Box 515, Folder 16)
    - Annual Meeting, 1974 (Box 515, Folder 17)
    - E. P. Broughton memorial gifts, 1974 (Box 519, Folder 5)
    - Board Members titles and bios, 1975 (Box 515, Folder 18)
    - Councilors correspondence, 1977 (Box 515, Folder 19)
    - [Annual Meeting invitation cards], 1977-1981 (Box 515, Folder 20)
    - Annual Meeting invitations, 1975 (Box 522, Folder 10)
    - 113th Annual Meeting and Dinner, 1977 (Box 522, Folder 11)
    - Select Committee Fundraising, 1977 (Box 523, Folder 1)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, 1977 (Box 523, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors meeting, May 31, 2977 (Box 523, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors correspondence, 1977 (Box 523, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee meetings, 1978 (Box 523, Folder 5-6)
    - Personnel Committee, 1979 (Box 558, Folder 10)
    - Name Change Committee, 1979 (Box 558, Folder 11)
    - Finance Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 523, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee meeting, January 31, 1973 (Box 530, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Special Meeting, February 24, 1973 (Box 530, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors Special Meeting, March 24, 1973 (Box 530, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee, April 25, 1973 (Box 530, Folder 7)
    - 109th Annual Meeting, May 14, 1973 (Box 530, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors meeting, May 21, 1973 (Box 530, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee, June 20, 1973 (Box 530, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors meeting, September 19, 1973 (Box 530, Folder 11)
    - Executive Committee, October 24, 1973 (Box 530, Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors meeting, November 14, 1973 (Box 530, Folder 13)
    - Executive Committee, December 19, 1973 (Box 530, Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors meeting, January 23, 1974 (Box 530, Folder 15)
    - Board of Directors meeting, February 27, 1974 (Box 530, Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee, March 27, 1974 (Box 530, Folder 17)
    - Board of Directors meeting, April 24, 1974 (Box 530, Folder 18)
    - 110th Annual Meeting, May 15, 1974 (Box 530, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors meeting, May 22, 1974 (Box 530, Folder 20)
    - Board of Directors meeting, June 19, 1974 (Box 530, Folder 21)